

Juan Antonio Vivaldy Saragih Front End Web Engineer

+62 821 4221 3434

- i juananthonio23@gmail.com

 i juananthonio23@gma
- https://juanantoniovivaldy.vercel.app/
- Medan, Indonesia

SUMMARY

Hello! My name is Juan Antonio Vivaldy Saragih and I enjoy creating things that live on the internet. My interest in web development started back in 2017 when I decided to join the website club at my highschool and make my own portfolio website with HTML & CSS!

Fast-forward to today, and I've had the privilege of working at Brighton, Tokohardware and Dealjava. My main focus right now is building and developing accessible and inclusive websites and new experiences for users. I also recently launched a course that covers everything you need to build a web app using Laravel & React.

EXPERIENCE

Front End Web Developer 07/2022 - Present

Dealjava

- Develop new web interface features and responsive website for users
- Maintaining and creating reusable components in React JS & Vue JS
- · Develop and migrate the websites from Vue JS to React JS
- · Designing and develop the admin site with user friendly web applications
- Designing a framework to create user applications that fit the needs of the company such as client side state management (Redux or Vuex)
- · Review application and feature front-end libraries and plan future use upgrades with the development team
- · Designing REST APIs using best practices methods in order to provide the best performance

Web Developer and UI/UX Designer

07/2021 - 06/2022

Tokohardware

- · Designing a website with a UI that matches the content
- Manage the website hosting for website maintenance
- Work with a variety of different languages, platforms, frameworks, and base front end development technologies such as HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, React, Vue, and WordPress
- · Manually tested sites in various browsers and mobile devices to ensure cross-browser compatibility and responsiveness

Front End Web Developer and Design Graphic

03/2021 - 06/2021

Brighton

- Design content for wedding invitations, packaging and offsets
- · Create and manage company website
- · Create a website for wedding invitations from clients
- · Designing content on social media

EDUCATION

Information Systems 2024

Mikroskil - Bachelor Degree

- Participating in National Level Competition (Hibah IWDM) 2022
- · Participate in National Level Competition (Gemastik) 2021
- Participate in Provincial Level Competitions (PKM) 2021

1/2

Natural Science 2020

Methodist 6 - Senior High School

- 1st Place in the National Level Robotics Competition 2019
- 2nd place in the North Sumatra Student Band Competition 2018

CERTIFICATES

CC0101EN: Introduction to Cloud Computing 05/2022 - Present

CAD101EN: Introduction to Cloud Development with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript 04/2022 - Present

PH125.2x: Data Science: Visualization 04/2022 - Present

CAD220EN Developing Cloud Applications with Node.js and React

04/2022 - Present

SKILLS

REST API HTML5 Advanced Expert CSS3 Laravel Intermediate Expert Javascript (ES6++) Expert Express JS Intermediate React JS Git Version Control Intermediate Expert Redux Advanced Figma Expert

Redux Advanced Figma Expert

Vue JS Advanced Visual Studio Code Expert

Vuex Advanced Intellij IDE Advanced

LANGUAGES

Indonesia Native English Fluent